inwear.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy- InWear

InWear knows that you care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.  Our privacy policy may be updated from time to time; we recommend that you check this page regularly to stay up to date on any changes we have made. 

IC Companys A/S is fully committed to respecting the privacy and security of your personal information. We are responsible for the processing of your personal data obtained on www.inwear.com/gb/ (the “Website"), and we will not disclose any information about you to third parties except when it is necessary for providing a service to you.

## Who are we?

www.inwear.com/gb/ is the official online store for InWear. InWear forms part of the IC Companys Group, and www.inwear.com/gb/ is operated under the laws of Denmark by the parent company IC Companys A/S (hereafter “we”). IC Companys A/S is a Danish listed group formed in 2001 by the merger of Carli Gry International A/S and InWear Group A/S. At present the IC Companys Group runs a portfolio of 11 strong fashion brands; e.g. Tiger of Sweden, Peak Performance, Jackpot, Cottonfield and Matinique, and has sales companies in 15 different countries - Denmark, Sweden, Norway, Finland, UK, Ireland, Germany, Holland, Belgium, Austria, France, Poland, the Czech Republic, Hungary and Canada.

IC Companys A/S is registered at the address:

IC Companys A/S

Raffinaderivej 10

DK-2300 Copenhagen S

Denmark

Tel.: +45 32 66 77 88

E-mail: hq@iccompanys.com

www.iccompanys.com

CVR. No: 62 81 64 14

## What information do we collect?

We collect information about you whenever you actively enter information on www.inwear.com/gb/. That is e.g. your name, address and preferences; when you sign up to become a InWear member online or in a shop, sign up for our newsletter, place an order, take part in a competition and/or participate in any other Website activities. 

We also collect information about you when you browse the Website. To provide an improved website experience, we use cookies and pixel tags. We may also collect traffic information to create trends and statistics.

## How may we use your personal information?

We automatically register you in our files when you actively enter personal information, (for example when placing an order or signing up for our newsletter). The information will be used for the purpose of which you have entered them.

To personalize and improve your website and shopping experience and make your shopping more convenient, we may also use any information about you gathered via www.inwear.com/gb/. The information allows us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you or our other customers in general are most interested. We also use the information to learn about our customers and be able to develop and provide tailored specific features.

### Communication and Marketing 

You will only receive information from InWear and www.inwear.com/gb/ if you opted in when you placed an order, or if you signed up to become a InWear member. 

If you change your mind, you can always opt out of receiving newsletters or any other service to which you have opted in. Any newsletter or promotion we send to you will contain an automated link, allowing you to opt out of that particular service.

### InWear membership

__As a InWear member you can enjoy great benefits:

  * Faster check out process
  * Receive offers on new items before they are available to others
  * Receive exclusive sales promotion
  * Track your orders
  * View your order history

When you become a InWear member, the information actively entered by you will be stored and saved by IC Companys A/S.

## Do we share your personal information with third parties?

We do not sell, share or transfer your personal information to any outside parties other than the companies within the IC Companys Group and our third party processors. 

For the sole purpose of operating our business, suppliers or third party processors (such as credit card companies, customer service providers and shipping companies) may process your information, but only to the extent that it is needed to assist the InWear business. We, as well as the IC Companys Group companies, have procedures to ensure that these third party processors value your privacy. 

Please note that we reserve the right to share personal information actively submitted by you on www.inwear.com/gb/ within the IC Companys Group, and the right to link this personal information with other personal information about you that other companies within the IC Companys Group may have obtained via other websites owned by the IC Companys Group. At present, the IC Companys Group runs 11 fashion brands and has sales companies in 16 different countries.  The shared information will solely be used for operating our business and used in order to give our customers a more convenient shopping experience, when shopping in our physical stores or with our other brands. You will never receive any communication or marketing from brands that you have not signed up to receive information from.

## Cookies

When you visit www.inwear.com/gb/ we collect information about your activities on our website (for example by using cookies). A cookie is a small data file placed on your computer’s hard drive containing information about which parts of our website you have visited. We use cookies to personalize your online experience and to collect statistical data for the purpose of improving the buying experience on the website. Cookies are reliable files and they cannot execute program code, transmit virus or be used to collect information about what you otherwise may use your computer for. We do not use cookies to store or collect personal information.

You are free to decline the use of cookies. Most web browsers permits to delete or block cookies and to warn you and ask for your consent before cookies are stored. You can find help in your internet browser on how to set your internet browser to handle and possible block cookies. If you do not wish to use cookies when visiting our online store this may affect your shopping experience, as we among other things use cookies to keep your shopping cart updated. The use of cookies is also necessary if you want to be able to place an order.

### What cookies do we use?

We use cookies for the following primary purposes; functionality, web statistics, sales and advertising.

We use the functional cookies to ensure that our online store is functioning as intended, which among other things includes that you are able to add items to your shopping cart, place an order etc. We do not store any personal information and the cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you close your browser. 

We use services from Google (Google Analytics) and Adobe (SiteCatalyst/Omniture) to collect web statistics. Cookies from these providers among other things allow us to see which pages are visited, where the traffic comes from etc. We use the information to measure and improve the user experience on our website and to follow up on sales and ad campaigns.

Additionally we use partners that help us to keep track of user activities, profitability of online marketing and to deliver targeted online ads when you visit other websites. These services may use third part cookies provided by our partners. To measure and optimise sales we use the following services:

  * AddThis
  * Adform
  * Google AdWords
  * Trade Tracker
  * 24/7 Media

## How can you gain access to, modify or remove information?

At any time you are entitled to recall the consent you have given with respect to our use of your personal information. Furthermore, you have the right to access your information and to review, and/or modify the information in the event your information stored by us is incorrect, and/or to delete the information. 

To modify your subscriptions or to completely opt-out of receiving InWear communication, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the “My Account” section of www.inwear.com/gb/ or click on the link in all of our newsletters to opt-out of that particular service. Due to e-mail production schedules, you may still receive any e-mails that are already in production. 

To delete your online InWear account, sign into the “My Account” section of the Website and click “Delete my account”. 

We store your information for 5 years after which it is deleted. If you wish to have your details removed from our information list or to gain access to your registered information, please contact our Customer Service Team who will be happy to assist you with your request. The stored information will not contain payment information such as credit card numbers, and we will not share your personal information with any third parties unless it is for the sole purpose of conducting your order.

## How do we protect your information?

www.inwear.com/gb/ uses one of the most secure online ordering systems on the market, and we are constantly researching and improving our software to make sure we offer the highest possible security at all times.

We utilise Security Socket Layer (SSL) technology; one of the most secure systems for ordering online that allows encryption of your potential sensitive information, such as your name and address and critical personal information such as credit card information. Your information will be encrypted from the moment you enter it, and your personal information will not be saved on a public server. That means that information passed between you and our Website cannot be read in the event someone else intercepts it. The SSL technology provides an authentication that assures your browser that your data is being sent to the correct secure computer server; an encryption that encodes all data, so only the secure server is able to read it; and a data integrity that checks that the transferred data has not been altered.

## Other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Any questions?

We are always happy to hear from you and welcome any questions, comments and concerns about privacy. Please visit the Contact Us page or write to us:

InWear

c/o GSI Commerce

Unit 26 Broadgate, Oldham Broadway Business Park

Chadderton, Manchester OL9 9XA

United Kingdom
